

MURSALIN SHEIKH

Solidity Engineer Web Developer

About Me

I am a technical enthusiast with a prior knowledge of 2 years in web development field as of now. Currently I am enhancing my skills in Full Stack development and Blockchain Development. Besides technical field, I have practiced Financial Management as a Marketing Enthusiast previously. I am an active learner always eager to learn new skills and gain new experiences in both technical and marketing field.

Projects

PROJECT

DESCRIPTION **EVENT MANAGEMENT**

This smart contract aims at providing facilities like Event organisation, ticket distribution, ticket transfer etc. This contract is deployed on Remix IDE, where it requires a Remix virtual machine along with Goerli testnet to manage ethereum which will be used while processing any transaction.

LANGUAGES USED Blockchain, Solidity

TIME November, 2022 - January, 2023

LINK github.com/mosabhai77/EventManager

PROJECT 2

META-DRIVE **DESCRIPTION**

This Dapp allows users to store and view their files on the IPFS network, as well as share them with other users on the network

IPFS, HARDHAT, SOLIDITY **LANGUAGES USED**

February, 2023 - March, 2023 TIME

LINK https://github.com/mosabhai77/Metadrive

PROJECT 3

FACE-RECOGNITION ATTENDANCE DATABASE DESCRIPTION

- Artificial Intelligence
- Machine Learning
- HOGG Algorithm

LANGUAGES USED Python, HTML

TIME November, 2021 - January, 2022

github.com/mosabhai77/Tyson-TheCollegeAssistant LINK

Professional Experience

FLUTTR

• Marketing Intern

November, 2021 - February, 2022

BINGE BEE

 Marketing Analyst March, 2021 - May, 2022

• Frontend Developer

PRABHAVATI DIGITAL SERVICES PVT. LTD. INDIA

June, 2022 - August, 2022

My Contact

mahigunda230@gmail.com

89267 42591

Chaya Bhawan, Tarulia 2nd Lane, Kestopur, 700102

Hard Skill

- Solidity (Advanced)
- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- C++, JAVA, PYTHON

Education Background

SECONDARY EDUCATION St Xavier's School Passed with 92%

HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION Burdwan Municipal High School Passed with 89%

B.TECH IN COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING University of Engineering and Management Pursuing

Personal Details

DATE OF BIRTH

27.10.2002

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English, Bengali, Hindi

NATIONALITY

INDIAN